

KMUTNB ,THAILAND

NAWAPAT THONGPITAKS



ABOUT ME

I like to develop myself constantly. When I encounter difficulties, I can also bring experience that helps solve problems. I like to find opportunities for myself. So getting this internship scholarship is a very good opportunity for me.

CONTACT

Phone 098-273-5672

Email

s6303051633069@email.kmutnb.ac.th

Address

Pathumthani, Thailand

EDUCATION

2014 - 2020

Ampornpaisarn School (Science-Math)

2020 - Present

Bachelor of Engineering Program in Electronics Engineering Technology (Computer)

EXPERTISE

- . HTML & CSS
- Database
- Python
- MS Office
- Electric Soldering

EXPERIENCE

• 2014 - 2020 : Ampornpaisarn School

Leadership skills

 When I was in high school, I got many leadership opportunities, whether classroom leaders, project manager, president of sport games and president of student council. Therefore, it has always given me the opportunity to cultivate my ability in the field of leadership.

CS Camp @KMITL

• I was selected to attend CS Camp organized by KMITL. That's about a computer science camp.

2020 - 2022 : KMUTNB

Mini Project

 In the second years, I had the opportunity from professor to do a mini project about the internal system development of scented candle stores. That's about Object-Oriented Progarmming.

President of student council

 This semester, I was elected as the president of the student council at KMUTNB. It was a good experience on the university life. Working in the student council give me a lot of experience and opportunities to make new friends.